{
  "LevelId": 28,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 281,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "PINCHBECK",
      "question": "alloy of copper and zinc, resembling gold, often used in jewelry"
    },
    {
      "id": 282,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "SMOKEJACK",
      "question": "device used to ventilate smoke from a fireplace or chimney"
    },
    {
      "id": 283,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "PICKABACK",
      "question": "term describes carrying someone on your back or shoulders"
    },
    {
      "id": 284,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "AUTODIALS",
      "question": "automated systems that make phone calls, often used for telemarketing or reminders"
    },
    {
      "id": 285,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "DIPSQUEAK",
      "question": "term is used to describe a small or insignificant person"
    },
    {
      "id": 286,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "CONJUGACY",
      "question": "mathematical term that refers to the relationship between two elements"
    },
    {
      "id": 287,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "MEXXANINE",
      "question": "compound containing a methyl group linked to two nitrogen atoms,"
    },
    {
      "id": 288,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "AMBERJACK",
      "question": "distinctive amber coloration and is commonly found in warm Atlantic waters"
    },
    {
      "id": 289,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "QYARTZITE",
      "question": "type of metamorphic rock is characterized by its hardness"
    },
    {
      "id": 290,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "EAGLEWOOD",
      "question": "wood is known for its fragrant and aromatic properties"
    },
    {
      "id": 291,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "QUADRATIC",
      "question": "mathematical equation involves a variable raised to the power of 2"
    },
    {
      "id": 292,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "TABESCENT",
      "question": "used to describe a fading color or a diminishing vitality"
    },
    {
      "id": 293,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "HEADQUARTERS",
      "question": "main office of an organization typically known as"
    }
  ]
}